Guide to the Jean Toomer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1920-54; Series II; 20.5; (49 boxes)
  - REVIEWS
    - Hoyland, John S. Indian Crisis (Box 57, Folder 1321)
    - Hummel, George F. After All, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1322)
    - Kelpius, Johannes. A Method of Prayer, edited by E. Gordon Alderfer, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 1323)
    - Kilvert, Francis. Kilvert's Diary, edited by William Plomer, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1324)
    - Lawrence, D. H. The Captain's Doll, [1923?] (Box 57, Folder 1325)
    - McKenzie, John G. Nervous Disorders, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 1326)
    - Munson, Gorham B. Waldo Frank: A Study: typescript, corrected by Gorham Munson, 1923 Mar (Box 57, Folder 1327)
    - Myers, L. H. The Orissers, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1328)
    - Palmer, W. Scott. The Confessions of Jacob Boehme, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1329)
    - The Path of the Saint, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1330)
    - Ridge, Lola. Dance of Fire, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1331)
    - Rosenfeld, Paul. Port of New York, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1332)
    - Rothermell, Fred. The Leaning Tower, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1333)
    - Sears, Paul B. This Is Our World, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1334)
  - SHORT STORIES
    - "Avey": typescript, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1335)
    - "Bona and Paul": typescript (Box 57, Folder 1336)
    - "Break": typescript, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1337)
      See also: Box 58, folder 1354
    - A Certain November: drafts, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1338)
      See also: Box 59, folder 1381
    - "Clinic"
      See: Box 58, folder 1364
    - "Easter": drafts & printed in The, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1339-41)
    - Little Review, 1925 spring
      See also: Box 59, folder 1386
    - Elise: typescript, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1342)
    - "The Family of Five": typescript (incomplete), n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1343)
    - "Fern": printed in The Little Review, vol. IX, no. 3, 1922 autumn (Box 57, Folder 1344)
    - "Fronts": drafts, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1345-46)
      See also: Box 58, folder 1358
      See also: Box 59, folder 1387
    - Hugh Lorimer Dreamed: typescript, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1347)
    - "Kabnis": printed in Broom, vol. 5, no. 2 and draft of review by Gorham Munson, 1923 Sep, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1348)
    - "Karintha": printed in Broom, vol. 4, no. 2, 1922 Jan (Box 57, Folder 1349)
    - "Lost and Dominant"
      - Notes, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1350)
      - Typescript: pages 1-55, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1351-52)
      - Typescript: pages 56-190, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1353-60)
    - Love on a Train: drafts (Box 58, Folder 1361-63)
      See also: Box 58, folder 1353, 1377 and Box 59, folder 1384
    - "Lump": typescript, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1364)
      See also: Box 59, folder 1383
    - Meridian Hill -- An Autobiographical Story: draft fragment, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1365)
    - "Mr. Costyve Duditch": notes, drafts, & printed in The Dial, vol. LXXXV, no. 6 (2 copies), 1928 Aug-Dec (Box 58, Folder 1366-68)
      See also: Box 57, folder 1352; Box 58 folder 1376; Box 59, folder 1382
    - "Mr. Limph Krok's Famous 'L' Ride": typescript (incomplete), n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1369)
      See also: Box 58, folder 1357
    - "Monrovia": typescript, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1370)
    - "Nora"
      See: Box 56, folder 1298
    - "Rhobert": typescript, 1922 Jul (Box 58, Folder 1371)
    - "Sheik and Anti-Sheik": typescript (Box 58, Folder 1372)
    - "Two Professors": drafts, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1373)
      See also: Box 58, folder 1356
    - "Winter on Earth": typescripts, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1374-75)
      See also: Box 58, folder 1380; Box 59, folder 1390
    - "Winter on Earth and Short Stories"
      - Early draft, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1376-80)
      - Later draft, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1381-90)
      - Later draft (carbon), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1391-94)
      - Book cover design, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 1395)
    - "Winter Road": drafts, 1937 Feb 26 (Box 59, Folder 1396)
    - "Withered Skin of Berries": typescript, 1922 May (Box 59, Folder 1397)
    - Unidentified short stories: drafts, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1398-99)
    - Unidentified writings: notes & fragments, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1400)
- Family Papers, 1898-1954; Series III; 3.5; (8 boxes)
  Boxes 60-67 hold Series III, Family Papers, which is divided into the papers of Bismarck Pinchback, Jean Toomer, and Margery Latimer Toomer. Each section is arranged alphabetically by type of material or subject. Jean Toomer's journals are arranged chronologically. Margery Latimer Toomer's writings, which contain drafts and published versions, are arranged alphabetically by title.
  - BISMARCK PINCHBACK
    - Journal (Box 59a, Folder 1401)
    - Poetry: holographs, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1402)
  - JEAN TOOMER
    - Advertisements, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1403)
    - Certificates and diplomas, 1917-31 (Box 60, Folder 1404)
    - Drawings and designs, 1901-05, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1405)
      See also: Box 73, folder 1639
    - Dupee, Charles: newspaper clippings, 1932-33 (Box 60, Folder 1406)
    - Dupee-Lowry Publishing, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1407)
    - Financial records, 1928-53 (Box 60, Folder 1408)
    - Journals
      - "Adolescent notes", [1912?] (Box 60, Folder 1409)
      - Memorandum notebook, [1920?] (Box 60, Folder 1410)
      - "Poetry" notebook, 1923 (Box 60, Folder 1411)
      - Notes, 1923-24 (Box 60, Folder 1412-13)
      - "New York" notebooks, 1924-26 (Box 60, Folder 1414-17)
      - "Tennants Harbor" notebook, 1925-26 (Box 60, Folder 1418)
      - "Paris" notebook, 1929-30 (Box 61, Folder 1419)
      - "Autobiography" notebook, 1929-30 (Box 61, Folder 1420)
      - Diary, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 1421)
      - Notes for "The Self Behind Me", 1937 Sep-Dec (Box 61, Folder 1422)
      - Notes, 1938 Jan-Mar (Box 61, Folder 1423-26)
      - "Psychological Diary": holographs, 1938 Apr-May (Box 61, Folder 1427-31)
      - "Psychological Diary": typescript, 1938 Apr-May (Box 61, Folder 1432)
      - Notes, 1939 Jan-Jul (Box 62, Folder 1433-34)
      - "India" notebook, 1939-40 (Box 62, Folder 1435)
      - Notes, 1940 Apr-Dec (Box 62, Folder 1436-37)
      - Notes, 1941 Jan-Oct (Box 62, Folder 1438-40)
      - Notes, 1946-47 (Box 62, Folder 1441)
      - "Dreams", 1949-50 (Box 62, Folder 1442-48)
      - "Notation of Events", 1949 May-Dec (Box 63, Folder 1449)
      - "Notation of Events", 1950 Jan-Jul (Box 63, Folder 1450-55)
      - Auditing notebooks I-IV, 1950-51 (Box 63, Folder 1456-59)
      - Notes about health, [1951?] (Box 64, Folder 1460)
      - "Case Books", 1951 Jan-Apr (Box 64, Folder 1461-67)
      - "V-M" notes, 1952 Feb-Apr (Box 64, Folder 1468)
      - Notes about Gurdjieff group meetings, 1953-54 (Box 64, Folder 1469-77)
      - Estimation of Margery Latimer's literary gifts, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1478)
      - "The Men and Women I Have Known" (Box 64, Folder 1479)
      - "Notes, Ideas, and Examples" (Box 64, Folder 1480)
      - "Terms of My Language", n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1481)
      - Notebook: contains notes about New Mexico, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1482)
      - Notebook: contains a reading list, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1483)
      - Unidentified fragments, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1484)
    - Legal papers, 1933-34 (Box 65, Folder 1485)
    - Library cards, 1918-48 (Box 65, Folder 1486)
    - Memorabilia, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1487)
    - Mill House documents, 1936 Aug 24 (Box 65, Folder 1488)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1923-32 (Box 65, Folder 1489)
    - Passports, 1926-40 (Box 65, Folder 1490)
    - Photographs, 1916-40, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1491-94)
      See also: Box 66, folder 1505; Box 73, folder 1639
    - Postcards, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1495)
    - Programs and tickets, 1931-52 (Box 65, Folder 1496)
    - Reading lists, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1497)
    - School papers, 1906-08 (Box 65, Folder 1498-1502)
    - School papers, 1909 Jan (Box 66, Folder 1503)
    - School papers: The Venetian Etchings of Whistler", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1504)
    - Scrapbook, 1914-17 (Box 66, Folder 1505)
    - Sparta Agricultural and Industrial Institute: brochures, 1921 (Box 66, Folder 1506)
      See also: Box 65, folder 1494
    - Trabuco: brochures, 1942 (Box 66, Folder 1507)
    - Toomer, Margery Latimer (daughter): memorabilia, 1933-51 (Box 66, Folder 1508)
    - Travel guides, 1926-27, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1509)
    - Turbyfill, Mark. "Bagging the Chicago Poet"
      See: Box 73, folder 1641
    - Yearbook: American College of Physical Education, 1917 (Box 66, Folder 1510)
  - MARGERY LATIMER TOOMER
    - Estate records, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 1511)
    - Journals: notes & notebook, 1924, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1512)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1932-34 (Box 66, Folder 1513)
    - Photographs, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 1514)
    - Schorer, Mark "Margery Latimer: Selections from a Correspondence" (Box 66, Folder 1515)
    - Writings
      - "The Child": typescript, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1516)
      - "The Eye": typescript, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1517)
      - "The Family": typescripts, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1518)
      - "Grotesque": printed in Transition, 1927 Jan (Box 66, Folder 1519)
      - "Me": printed in The Reviewer, vol. IV, no. 1, 1923 Oct (Box 66, Folder 1520)
      - "Mr. and Mrs. Arnold": printed in The Reviewer, vol. IV, no. 3 (2 copies), 1924 Apr (Box 67, Folder 1521)
      - "Nellie Bloom": printed in The Bookman, vol. LXVI, no. 3, 1927 Nov (Box 67, Folder 1522)
      - "The New Freedom": printed in The Reviewer, vol. IV, no. 2, 1924 Jan (Box 67, Folder 1523)
      - "O Clouds Roll Back": typescript, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1524)
      - "Penance": typescript, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1525)
      - "The Ship": typescript, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1526-29)
      - "Spring": typescript, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1530)
      - "The Struggle": notes & typescripts, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1531)
      - "Werwolf": printed in The Century, vol. III, no. 6, 1926 Apr (Box 67, Folder 1532)
      - "Wind": printed in The Reviewer, vol. IV, no. 4 (2 copies), 1924 Jul (Box 67, Folder 1533)
      - "Winter": typescripts, 1928 Apr 3 (Box 67, Folder 1534)
      - Unidentified: draft fragments, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1535)
- Related Papers, 1904-58; Series IV; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  Boxes 68-70 hold Series IV, Related Papers, which is divided into the papers of Georges Gurdjieff, Society of Friends, Subject Files, and Writings of Others. Each section is arranged alphabetically by type of material, subject, author, or title. Georges Gurdjieff's papers include his lectures and writings and information about him and various Gurdjieff groups. The Society of Friends section includes reports of various committees in addition to Society pamphlets and publications. Subject Files contain newspaper clippings, articles, and pamphlets arranged alphabetically by subject. Writings of Others consists exclusively of manuscripts, arranged alphabetically by author.
  - GEORGES GURDJIEFF
    - Bennett, John G.: lectures & publicity, 1952-54 (Box 68, Folder 1536)
    - "G. Gurdjieff's Institute for the Harmonious Development of Man": pamphlet (3 copies), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1537)
    - "Gurdjieff's List of Russian-English Words of Command": typescript (Box 68, Folder 1538)
    - Lectures: transcripts, 1921-29 (Box 68, Folder 1539)
    - Lectures: notes & publicity, 1930-39 (Box 68, Folder 1540)
    - Lectures: transcripts, 1941-44 (Box 68, Folder 1541)
    - Lectures: drafts, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1542)
    - Orage, A. R.: transcripts of his meetings, 1925 Jan-Dec (Box 68, Folder 1543)
    - Orage, A. R.: transcripts of his meetings, 1926 Jan-Apr (Box 68, Folder 1544)
    - Photographs, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1545)
    - "Sayings of G. G.": notes in the hand of Jean Toomer (Box 68, Folder 1546)
    - Toomer, Jean: notes about his Gurdjieff groups, 1925-31, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1547)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd: typescript of "George Gurdjief at Taliesin", 1934 Sep 12 (Box 68, Folder 1548)
    - Writings
      Beelzebub's Tales to His Grandson
      - Outlines, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1549)
      - Notes: typescripts, 1927 Jan-Apr (Box 68, Folder 1550)
      - Notes by Jean Toomer, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1551)
      - "Warning": typescript, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1552)
      - "Why Beelzebub was on Our Solar System": typescript, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1553)
      - "First Descent of Beelzebub on the Earth": typescript, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1554)
      - "Tales of Beelzebub about His Second Descent to the Planet Earth": typescript (Box 68, Folder 1555)
      - "The Third Flight of Beelzebub to the Planet Earth": typescript, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1556)
      - "The Fourth Visit of Beelzebub to the Planet Earth": typescript, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1557)
      - "Flight of Beelzebub to the Planet Earth for the Fifth Time": typescript, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1558-59)
      - "The Planet Purgatory", n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1560)
      - "The History Related by Beelzebub": typescript, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1561)
      - "Beelzebub's Opinion on War": typescript, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1562)
      - "The Outer and Inner World of Man": typescript (Box 69, Folder 1563)
      - "The Struggle of the Magicians": draft in Jean Toomer's hand (Box 69, Folder 1564)
      - Reviews, 1933, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1565)
  - SOCIETY OF FRIENDS
    - Articles about Friends, 1937, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1566)
    - Buckingham Quarterly Committee: reports, 1946 Feb 23 (Box 69, Folder 1567)
    - Buckingham School Committee: notes & reports, 1945 Nov-Dec (Box 69, Folder 1568)
    - Buckingham Social Service Committee: notes & reports, 1942, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1569)
    - Friends Committee on National Legislation: newsletters, 1945-48 (Box 69, Folder 1570)
    - Friends Intelligencer, 1944-54 (Box 69, Folder 1571-72)
    - Friends Yearly Meeting: reports (Box 69, Folder 1573)
    - National Council Against Conscription: newsletters, 1946-47 (Box 69, Folder 1574)
    - Pamphlets, 1945-52 (Box 69, Folder 1575)
  - SUBJECT FILES
    - Art (Box 70, Folder 1576)
    - Education, 1936-40, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1577)
    - India, 1928-40 (Box 70, Folder 1578)
    - Literature: book reviews, 1929-38 (Box 70, Folder 1579)
    - New Mexico, 1936-38 (Box 70, Folder 1580)
    - Psychology and religion, 1923-51 (Box 70, Folder 1581)
    - Race relations, 1904-38 (Box 70, Folder 1582)
    - Science, 1928-50 (Box 70, Folder 1583)
    - Social history, 1929-40 (Box 70, Folder 1584)
    - World War, 1939-1945, 1935-55 (Box 70, Folder 1585)
  - WRITINGS OF OTHERS
    - Babson, Roger: outline of "Fifty Ways to Make a Million Dollars!" (Box 70, Folder 1586)
    - Bliss, Caroline M.: typescript, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1587)
    - Crane, Hart: drawings & drafts, 1923, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1588)
    - Grove, Max: typescript, 1931 Jan 18 (Box 70, Folder 1589)
    - Grove, Shirley: typescript, 1931 Jan 20 (Box 70, Folder 1590)
    - Jones, Rufus M.
      See: Box 53, folder 1180
    - Lane, Jeremy: typescript, 1930-32 (Box 70, Folder 1591)
    - Latimer, Clark Watt: typescript, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1592)
    - Loüys, Pierre: typescript of "Aphrodite", n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1593)
    - Luhan, Mabel Dodge: typescripts of "Best to Tell All" and "Tell Me Master" (Box 70, Folder 1594)
    - M., D. M.: typescript of "Saturday Afternoon", n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1595)
    - McDonald, G. I.: typescript, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1596)
    - Michener, James A.: typescript of "A Quaker Passport", n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1597)
    - Morris, Holdaah: typescript of "Science of Numbers", 1928 (Box 70, Folder 1598)
    - Peters, Fritz: typescript of "The Book of Toby", 1932 Jul 12 (Box 70, Folder 1599)
    - "Superstitions": notes by Lea, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1600)
    - Williams, Nadja: holograph, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1601)
- Printed Works, 1917-53; Series V; 1; (2 boxes)
  Boxes 71-72 hold Series V, Printed Works. Magazines and pamphlets are interfiled alphabetically by title with the authors of books and brochures.
  - American Pigeon Journal, 1936 Feb (Box 71, Folder 1602)
  - L'Automobile et L'Effort Français, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1603)
  - Baldwin, Louis Fremont. From Negro to Caucasian, 1929 (Box 71, Folder 1604)
  - Black Opals, vol. 1, no. 4, 1928 Dec (Box 71, Folder 1605)
  - Blues, vol. 1, no. 1, 1929 Feb (Box 71, Folder 1606)
  - The Carmelite
  - Le Carrefour, no. 23, 1929 Oct 17 (Box 71, Folder 1607)
  - The Chicagoan, 1928-31 (Box 71, Folder 1608)
  - Contempo, vol. II, no. 1, 1932 May 5 (Box 71, Folder 1609)
  - Cunard, Nancy. Black Man and White Ladyship, 1931 (Box 71, Folder 1610)
  - The Dial, 1922 Nov (Box 71, Folder 1611)
  - The Dial, 1926 Jul-Aug (Box 71, Folder 1612)
  - The Dial, 1928-29 (Box 71, Folder 1613)
  - The Dramatists' Guild. "Managers' List", 1933 Nov (Box 71, Folder 1614)
  - Edgar Cayce His Life and Work: printed by The Association for Research and Enlightenment, 1941 Jul (Box 71, Folder 1615)
  - Experimental Schools: bulletin no. 4 of the Bureau of Educational Experiments, 1917 (Box 71, Folder 1616)
  - 4D: printed essays, 1928-29 (Box 71, Folder 1617)
  - Inside Baseball, vol. 1, no. 6, 1953 Jan (Box 71, Folder 1618)
  - The Jews in Nazi Germany: copyright by the American Jewish Committee, 1933 (Box 72, Folder 1619)
  - Kelm, William Eulberg. Let's Be Fashionable, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1620)
  - Kreisselmeier: brochure, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1621)
  - Kurt Wolff Verlag München: brochure, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1622)
  - The Macaulay Folio: brochure, 1928 fall (Box 72, Folder 1623)
  - Mental Health News, 1949 Jan (Box 72, Folder 1624)
  - The Nation, 1928, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 1625)
  - The New Republic, 1928, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 1626)
  - Outlook and Independent, vol. 158, no. 17, 1931 Aug 26 (Box 72, Folder 1627)
  - Playboy
    See: Box 73, folder 1642
  - The Playgoer, vol. 34, no. 10, 1927 Nov 7 (Box 72, Folder 1628)
  - Roerich Museum: Journal of Urusvati & advertisement for Realm of Light, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 1629)
  - Salient, 1929 Jan-Mar (Box 72, Folder 1630)
  - The Saturday Evening Quill, no. 2, 1929 Apr (Box 72, Folder 1631)
  - Scribner's, vol. XC, no. 2 (2 copies), 1931 Aug (Box 72, Folder 1632)
  - Secession, no. 5, 1923 Jul (Box 72, Folder 1633)
  - The Star, vol. 1, no. 9, 1928 Sep (Box 72, Folder 1634)
  - Time, 1937-38 (Box 72, Folder 1635)
  - T-Square, vol. 2, no. 2, 1932 Feb (Box 72, Folder 1636)
  - The Walden School: brochure, 1923-24 (Box 72, Folder 1637)
  - Workshop for Cultural Democracy: newsletter, vol. 1, no. 2, 1947 winter (Box 72, Folder 1638)
- Oversize, 1923-32; 1.5; (2 boxes)
  The Oversize material contains papers from Series III and V and is arranged in the same order as material in those series.
  - FAMILY PAPERS
    - Photographs of Jean Toomer, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 1639)
    - Turbyfill, Mark. "Bagging the Chicago Poet": typescript & printed in The Chicagoan, 1932 Mar (Box 73, Folder 1640)
    - Bismark Pinchback: journal, 1898-99 (Box 73, Folder 1640a)
  - PRINTED WORKS
    - The Carmelite, vol. 1, no. 29, 1928 Aug 29 (Box 73, Folder 1641)
    - Playboy, vol. 2, no. 1, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 1642)
  - FAMILY PAPERS
    - Drawings and designs (Box 74, Folder 1643)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 8; (19 boxes)
  Boxes 75-92, contain fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 1 (Box 75, Folder 1644)
  - Box 1, folder 5 (Box 75, Folder 1645)
  - Box 1, folders 7-8 (Box 75, Folder 1646)
  - Box 1, folder 10 (Box 75, Folder 1647)
  - Box 1, folder 11 (Box 75, Folder 1648)
  - Box 1, folder 13 (Box 75, Folder 1649)
  - Box 1, folder 18 (Box 75, Folder 1650)
  - Box 1, folders 23-24 (Box 75, Folder 1651)
  - Box 1, folders 26-27 (Box 75, Folder 1652)
  - Box 1, folder 29 (Box 75, Folder 1653)
  - Box 1, folders 30-31 (Box 75, Folder 1654)
  - Box 1, folder 34 (Box 75, Folder 1655)
  - Box 1, folders 36-37, 39-40 (Box 75, Folder 1656)
  - Box 1, folder 43 (Box 75, Folder 1657)
  - Box 2, folder 44 (Box 75, Folder 1658)
  - Box 2, folders 45-46 (Box 75, Folder 1659)
  - Box 2, folder 48 (Box 75, Folder 1660)
  - Box 2, folders 53-54, 57 (Box 75, Folder 1661)
  - Box 2, folders 58-59, 61-62 (Box 75, Folder 1662)
  - Box 2, folders 64-65, 68, 70, 74-75 (Box 75, Folder 1663)
  - Box 3, folder 76 (Box 75, Folder 1664)
  - Box 3, folder 77 (Box 75, Folder 1665)
  - Box 3, folders 78, 83-84, 86-89 (Box 75, Folder 1666)
  - Box 3, folders 90-92, 94-95 (Box 75, Folder 1667)
  - Box 3, folders 96-98 (Box 75, Folder 1668)
  - Box 3, folder 99 (Box 75, Folder 1669)
  - Box 3, folder 100 (Box 75, Folder 1670)
  - Box 3, folders 101, 105-06 (Box 75, Folder 1671)
  - Box 4, folder 109 (Box 76, Folder 1672)
  - Box 4, folders 110-11 (Box 76, Folder 1673)
  - Box 4, folder 112 (Box 76, Folder 1674)
  - Box 4, folders 113, 115-16, 121 (Box 76, Folder 1675)
  - Box 4, folder 122 (Box 76, Folder 1676)
  - Box 4, folders 123, 126, 132, 135 (Box 76, Folder 1677)
  - Box 4, folder 136 (Box 76, Folder 1678)
  - Box 4, folder 137 (Box 76, Folder 1679)
  - Box 4, folders 139-41, 145 (Box 76, Folder 1680)
  - Box 4, folder 146 (Box 76, Folder 1681)
  - Box 4, folder 147 (Box 76, Folder 1682)
  - Box 4, folder 148 (Box 76, Folder 1683)
  - Box 4, folder 149 (Box 76, Folder 1684)
  - Box 5, folder 151 (Box 76, Folder 1685)
  - Box 5, folder 152 (Box 76, Folder 1686)
  - Box 5, folder 153 (Box 76, Folder 1687)
  - Box 5, folders 154, 156 (Box 76, Folder 1688)
  - Box 5, folder 157 (Box 76, Folder 1689)
  - Box 5, folders 160-61 (Box 76, Folder 1690)
  - Box 5, folder 163 (Box 76, Folder 1691)
  - Box 5, folders 165, 168-71 (Box 76, Folder 1692)
  - Box 5, folder 172 (Box 76, Folder 1693)
  - Box 5, folders 173, 176, 178, 180-82 (Box 76, Folder 1694)
  - Box 6, folders 183, 185-88, 190 (Box 76, Folder 1695)
  - Box 6, folders 191-93, 197 (Box 76, Folder 1696)
  - Box 6, folders 200, 202-03, 205-06 (Box 76, Folder 1697)
  - Box 6, folders 208-10, 213 (Box 76, Folder 1698)
  - Box 7, folders 216, 219, 223-34 (Box 77, Folder 1699)
  - Box 7, folder 226 (Box 77, Folder 1700)
  - Box 7, folders 227, 232-34 (Box 77, Folder 1701)
  - Box 7, folders 235-38 (Box 77, Folder 1702)
  - Box 7, folders 239-40 (Box 77, Folder 1703)
  - Box 7, folder 241 (Box 77, Folder 1704)
  - Box 7, folders 242-43 (Box 77, Folder 1705)
  - Box 8, folders 244, 246-47, 250-52 (Box 77, Folder 1706)
  - Box 8, folders 253-56 (Box 77, Folder 1707)
  - Box 8, folders 259-61 (Box 77, Folder 1708)
  - Box 8, folder 264 (Box 77, Folder 1709)
  - Box 8, folders 266-68, 270 (Box 77, Folder 1710)
  - Box 8, folders 271-72, 274-76 (Box 77, Folder 1711)
  - Box 8, folder 277 (Box 77, Folder 1712)
  - Box 8, folder 278 (Box 77, Folder 1713)
  - Box 9, folder 281 (Box 77, Folder 1714)
  - Box 9, folder 283 (Box 77, Folder 1715)
  - Box 9, folders 285, 296 (Box 77, Folder 1716)
  - Box 9, folder 298 (Box 77, Folder 1717)
  - Box 9, folder 303 (Box 77, Folder 1718)
  - Box 9, folder 304 (Box 77, Folder 1719)
  - Box 9, folder 307 (Box 77, Folder 1720)
  - Box 9, folder 309 (Box 77, Folder 1721)
  - Box 9, folder 310 (Box 77, Folder 1722)
  - Box 10, folder 311 (Box 78, Folder 1723)
  - Box 10, folder 312 (Box 78, Folder 1724)
  - Box 10, folder 313 (Box 78, Folder 1725)
  - Box 10, folder 314 (Box 78, Folder 1726)
  - Box 10, folder 315 (Box 78, Folder 1727)
  - Box 10, folder 316 (Box 78, Folder 1728)
  - Box 10, folder 317 (Box 78, Folder 1729)
  - Box 10, folder 323 (Box 78, Folder 1730)
  - Box 10, folder 325 (Box 78, Folder 1731)
  - Box 10, folder 327 (Box 78, Folder 1732)
  - Box 10, folder 329 (Box 78, Folder 1733)
  - Box 10, folder 333 (Box 78, Folder 1734)
  - Box 10, folders 334-35, 338 (Box 78, Folder 1735)
  - Box 11, folder 358 (Box 78, Folder 1736)
  - Box 11, folder 359 (Box 78, Folder 1737)
  - Box 11, folder 360 (Box 78, Folder 1738)
  - Box 11, folder 361 (Box 78, Folder 1739)
  - Box 11, folder 362 (Box 78, Folder 1740)